{
    "id": "ebe73e6c276b494daedb040070a42b8c",
    "title": "Verb Conjugation",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Maya ............................................ since morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is working",
                "works",
                "has been working"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d8d244eafc3d4ef4a1d29ce27f397ae6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ...................................... in the garden, when he arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am working",
                "was working",
                "worked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4c73a2c0ebe64b53ae5a814cb2b79207"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................................... in the garage for three hours when John called.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have been working",
                "was working",
                "had been working"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "73b4c7d5cccf4b8db4215c9fe71c5cf8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ............................................. my exam this time next week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be writing",
                "will write",
                "would be writing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ddae11e4eaf84633925548a09ba4e3bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "They had already left by the time I .............................................. home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "reached",
                "have reached",
                "had reached"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "677042c8dc63425ab3f5adaa3e226ebe"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘I’m hungry.’ 'I .......................................................... you something to eat.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am getting",
                "will get",
                "will be getting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ec8a7fd0cccf4e9ca8b593a917bc4b0a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Merlin .................................................... lovely songs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "writes",
                "write",
                "written"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e06845286c514504a313347d1753b6ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ........................................................ often go to the cinema.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "don't",
                "doesn't",
                "haven't"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "759adad5466a45f3bfde0c2ca01ddbc7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ...................................................... to Philadelphia last week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "have gone",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b7ab12f2eb1649aeac7ee3710d538040"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children ........................................................ a splendid performance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "delivers",
                "deliver",
                "delivered"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "716901d1c9bd43dd9b64f2474638693b"
        }
    ]
}